{
    "id": "3fa4196cc12449fabf9f131f886a9f62",
    "title": "Can, Could, Will, Would",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ran as fast as he ………………………..",
            "description": "Could indicates past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "wouldCol"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec28f4d157ec4b279f7caffbabff4347"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… swim when she was just three.",
            "description": "Could indicates past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "623b98d4520444f4bb06080d6a1ad7ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju ……………………….. speak six languages.",
            "description": "Can is used to make a request, to ask for permission or to express ability to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "423b7b9d6fcd49d2854240aee6b53af5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think I ………………………….. pass the test.",
            "description": "Will is used to predict something, to express willingness or to announce a spontaneous decision.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0754b1ea86574f039bf35ca04a6cca2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He failed the test because he …………………………….. answer only 2 questions.",
            "description": "Could shows past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1470c52d9d0945d088c7e0d271cc4b1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ……………………….. help but he didn’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "384833db5a60442d92ba80b201b7b78f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had enough money, I ………………………….. travel around the world.",
            "description": "Would is the past form of will.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9265e7efbd8e4d6c97bb9fbb8e7c5b57"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I …………………………… get that mole examined.",
            "description": "Would is the past form of will.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "336d3cdc7b344ac6bd4b68317bb834cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. borrow my car if you want.",
            "description": "Can is used to make a request, to ask for permission or to express ability to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b130909d4c3a4fa2bd9c2240890bdb1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ……………………………. cook dinner today?",
            "description": "Will is used to predict something, to express willingness or to announce a spontaneous decision.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c08c5c3cf24646d9abe78f906bf2ddcc"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you like to dance with me?",
            "description": "Would is used in polite requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "96d4e81daa4341c9a930dc68069121f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried to solve the problem, but I …………………………...",
            "description": "Could not shows past inability. ",
            "answers": [
                "cannot",
                "could not",
                "would not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29b424fb266f4c7c96d6fd82fa30120c"
        }
    ]
}